# Olabode Iyanu Emmanuel

**☎**: (+234)8031828292 **☎**: iyanuolabode@yahoo.com

No 11, Stallion Street, Kolapo Ishola G.R.A, Ibadan

#### **Customer Service Representative**

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Customer Service Representative with over 4 years of experience in telephone customer service, including sales, tech support and customer care. Familiar with major customer service software and conflict resolution and possess a positive attitude. Aiming to use my proven skills effectively in your organization.

#### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- Microsoft Office
- Network Security
- Digital Marketing

- Quality Control and Assurance
- International Development
- Photography

- Teamwork
- Communication

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Business Development manager | Seed of Faith Block Industry | October 2022- Present

- Researching, planning and implementing new target customer areas
- Marketing of products and services on social media platforms and in persons to prospective clients
- Arrange business meetings with prospective clients
- Developing quotes and proposals for prospective clients
- Supervising production of blocks and rendering of services to clients

# Sales executive | Seed of Faith Block Industry | January 2022- September 2022

- Presenting the products and services to the customers
- Working on collaboration with the business development manager
- Meeting the monthly sales goals and expectations
- Taking feedbacks from the customers and working upon them in collaboration with the business development manager
- Resolving customers complaints and issues of any before and after making the sale
- Building a strong and positive relationship with the customers.

#### Business Development manager | Infitouch Technologies | August 2021 - December 2021

- Determining the potential business opportunities
- Marketing of services on social media platforms and in persons to prospective clients
- Developing a good relationship with customers and partners
- Implementing new business development strategies to Maximize profit and sales
- Supervising services rendered when carrying out field works

#### Customer Service Consultant | Infitouch Technologies | March 2020 - August 2021

- Marketing of services on social media platforms and in persons to prospective clients
- Understanding the client's needs and requirements
- Providing customer satisfaction through negotiation
- Identifying client's concerns and queries
- Taking orders from the clients
- Answering all the queries faced by the clients via email or phone

# Laboratory assistant | University of Agriculture, Abeokuta | May 2019- February 2020

- Setting up laboratory equipment and appliances for student's practicals
- Carrying out biological laboratory analysis
- Keeping records of students laboratory practices
- Creating reports, typing and writing documents that support laboratory
- Working on analysis, giving out results and feedbacks to clients (undergraduates, postgraduates and other researchers) from other schools and within.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Technology - Science Laboratory Technology

Ladoke Akintola University of Technology, Ogbomoso 2018 Second Class Honors (Lower Division).

# CERTIFICATIONS

The fundamentals of Digital Marketing, Google 2019

Network Security Expert level 1 2021
International Development, Dataville LLC 2022